Guide to the Sylvère Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive MSS.221
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries A: Individuals
    - Ray, Nicca (includes ms 'Cherry Bomb'), undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Ray, Nicca, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Ray, Nicca, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Ready-Made, Blanche, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Reale, Egidio, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Reeder, Claudia, 1974-5 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Rehberger, John, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Reifenberg, Odor Or, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Reimers, Ronald (Palimpsest Review), 1982 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - [Rejuie-Bille, D.], 1975 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Ren-Lay, Judith, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - [Rerret], Elizabeth, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Rey, [Jean], 1974 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Ricardou, Jean, 1970-7 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Richard, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Richard, Jean [Curro], [1964] (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Richard, Pascale, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Richards, Gary V., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Ridless, Robin, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Riffaterre, Michael, 1971-98 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Robbe-Grillet, Catherine, 1980-98 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Robbins, Joanne, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Robert, Alfred, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Robert, Marine, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Roberts, Mark, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Roche, Maurice, 1984-6 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Rodrigo, Nandi, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Rolnick, Suely (also signs as Suely Zolnick), 1986-90 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Romondino, Annalisa, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Ron, undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - [Rosdiansyah], 1995 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Rosemary, 1981-2 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - [Rosenbaum, Andy], 1981 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Rossi, Paul Louis, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Rotert, Alfred, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - [Rothenberg, Pierre], 1961 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Rothenberger, Manfred (Bakena), 1990 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Roubichou, Gerard (Ambassade de France), 1978 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Roudiez, Leon S. (Chair, Columbia French Dept.), 1971-2 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Rower, Ann, 1988-93 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - "RU: anarcho-pacifist", 1987 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - [Rubin, Jerry], 1983 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Rukavina, Gregory, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Russell, Allan, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Russell, Bertrand, 1961-2 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Russo, Adelaide, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Ruth, undated (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Rutherford-Dyer, Robert, 1977-86 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Ryan, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Ryan, Paul, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - "S", 1983 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - "S", 1985 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - "S", undated (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - "S", undated (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - "S", undated (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Sabina, undated (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Sackville-West, Vita, 1961-2 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Saenger, Elizabeth, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Said, Edward, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - [Saint-Amant, Dina], 1995 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - [Sairita-Jean], Natalie, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Salmon, Barbara, 1983-4 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Sampsell, Kevin (Snipehunt), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Sanders, Ed, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Sandlin, David, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Sarraute, Nathalie, 1963-83 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Sartorius, Joachim, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - [Sayari, Michael], 1980 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - [Scatt, Zack], undated (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Scheer, Edward, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - [Scheer, S.], 1974 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Schefer, Jean Louis, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Scheff, Janet, 1983-7 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Schein, Lorraine, undated (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - [Schickling], Janet, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Schneeman, Carolee, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - Schoenbaum, Sam, undated (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - Schoener, Allon, 1985-8 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - Scholder, Amy (City Lights), 1992 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Schulman, Peter, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Schulman, Sarah, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Schutze, Bernard, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Schwartz, Leonard, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Scranton, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Seamus, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Seaver, Richard, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Seem, Mark, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Seglard, Dominique, 1990-9 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - [Seguret, Eve], 1983 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - [Sekerci, Bursun], 1969 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - [Selkow, Bettina], 1984 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Sellers, Terence, 1982-92 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Seras, Alexandra, 1983-4 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Serge, undated (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - [Seth], 1979 (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Shafir, Yvonne, 1994-5 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - "Shake", undated (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - [Shaldeve, Valerie], 1983 (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Shapazian, Robert (Lapis Press), 1986-7 (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - Sherman, Stuart, 1980-91 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Sherpa, Laure, 1982-5 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Shiba, Shunichi, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Shirley, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Sidelsky, Monique "Nitza", 1957-99 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - [Sievernine], Lilyan, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Silverberg, Ira, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - Silverman, Michael, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - Simon, undated (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - Simon, Claude, 1972-83 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Simon, Isabelle, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - Simons, Martin, [1985] (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - Sitwell, Osbert, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - Sivadon-Sabourin, Danielle, 1992-9 (Box 5, Folder 145)
    - [Sksanlik, Myriam], [1986] (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - Skwazczewska, Alicja, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Slater, Howard, c. 1995 (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - Sloly, Matthew, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 149)
    - Smith, Duncan, 1980-6 (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Sontag, Susan, [1997] (Box 5, Folder 151)
    - [Sorguz], 1969 (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - Sotenberg, Marechal des Logis, 1957-8 (Box 5, Folder 153)
    - [Spald], undated (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - Spanos, William V. (Boundary 2), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - Spaulings, Reena, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - Spaziani, Paolo and Corsini, Letizia, undated (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - Spero, Nancy, 1992-2003 (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - Spivak, Gayatri, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - Spurlock, Kim, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - Stadler, Matthew, 1990-3 (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - Stallings, Tyler, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - Stanistreet, Peter, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - Starobinski, Jean, 1964-74 (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - Steir, Pat, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - Steph, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - [Stermicha, Mme.], 1962 (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - Stern, Dagmar, 1982-7 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - Steve (Case Western), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - Steven, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - Stewart, Clifford, undated (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Stivale, Charles, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Stoller, Robert J., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Strauss, Neil, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Suateric, Ales, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - [Surya], Michel, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Susan, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Susanna, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Suzan, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Sweet, David, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Swezey, Ken, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Sylvie, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Sylvie, 1984-5 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Szasz, Thomas, 1977-8 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - T, Mick, 1995-7 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Tabatoni, Pierre (Ambassade de France), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Takahashi, Yuji, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Talbot, Patrick (Ambassade de France), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Tarrida, Quim, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Tassel, Alice, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - [Tbtru, Mahomet Abby], 1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Thevenin, Paule, 1989-90 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Thorstad, David, 1983-94 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Tickell, Paul (BBC Television), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Tiefenbrun, Susan W., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Tillett, Seth, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Tillman, Joseph A., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Tillman, Lynne, 1990-4 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Timmons, Susie, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Tnouah, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Todorov, Tzvetan, 1969-72 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Toly-Thiercelin, Carine, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Tong, Diane, [1980] (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Torton, Stephen, c. 1983 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - [Toxe, Alain], 1982 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Tracy, undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Tromans, Richard, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Tsang, Daniel, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Tsoutas, Nicholas, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Tupahache, Asiba, c. 1992 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Turner, James, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Tweedie, Merylyn, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Tytell, Pam, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Undapresha, Grace, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Uno, Kumiichi, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Vaaler, Denise, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Valesio, Paolo, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Vallejo, Lupe, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Vanessa, 1977-8 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Van Roden Allen, Robert, 1978-80 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Vassas, Odile (DAAD), 1991 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Vaugeois, Gerard, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - [Vendglasen, Doc], undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Verdiglione, Armando, 1980-1 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Viallet, Laurence, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Viegener, M., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Virilio, Paul, 1981-8 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Virilio, Paul, 1990-9 (Box 6, Folder 573)
    - Virilio, Paul, 2000-6 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Virilio, Paul, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Vitoux, Frederic, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - [Vitoux, Frinine], 1974-87 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - [Vitoux, Nicole], 1992 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Vollmann, William T., 1991-2 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Von, undated (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Von der Ahe, Jess, 1992-9 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - W, Peter, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Wahl, Francois (Editions du Seuil), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Walborsky, Lisa, undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Waliszek, Astrid, 1981-8 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Waltemath, Joan, 1988-90 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Walter (Case Western), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Walter, Edith, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Walters, Beth and Ray, 1969-70 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Watts, Phil, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - [Wearn, Theodore], 1999 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - [Weber, Gentram], 1984 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Wechsler, Elayne, [1986] (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Wedele, Noura, undated (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - [Weems, Marianne], 1986 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Weil, Brian, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Wehrli, Penelope, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Weiner, [C.], 1992 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Weirich, Susanne, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Weiss, Allen S., 1982-90 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Weiss, Anne-Marie, 1985-6 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Weiss, [Jonita], undated (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Welchman, John C., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Welsh, William, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Wetzel, Kraft, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - [Wewerka], Alexander, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Wheeler, Susan, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - White, Emil, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - White, John, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Whitefeather, Selena, 1977-9 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Wilke, Hannah, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Wilkes, Marielle (Art Center), 1996 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Willener, Alfred, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Wilson, Leila, undated (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Wilson, Peter L., undated (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Wise, Matthew, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Witkin, Joel Peter, c. 1983 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Wolfson, Louis, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Wongpanlert, Thanya, 1994-2000 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Wongpanlert, Thanya, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Wongpanlert, Thanya, undated (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Woodbury, Jennifer, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Woolf, Leonard, 1961-7 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Wortsman, Peter, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Wulf, Christoph, 1982-9 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Yaddo, undated (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Yamagato, Hiroo, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Youssi, Helene, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Zaya (Blanco), 1979 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Zee, Mina, 1991-2 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Zeitlan, Hraztan (editor of Architecture Issue), 1990 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - [Zilvek], Jacqueline, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Zivancevic, Nina, 1992-8 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Zorrilla, Oscar, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Zubizarreta, Armando, undated (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Zurbrugg, Nicholas, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Subseries B: Organizations
    Materials have been arranged alphabetically by name of sender-organization. Because this series contains both Sylvère Lotringer's personal correspondence and that of Semiotext(e), it includes letters addressed to recipients other than Lotringer, such as Jim Fleming and Chris Kraus. These letters are nevertheless filed under the name of their sender. Files may include manuscripts, photographs and other material that was included with the letters. Materials in each folder are arranged chronologically, with undated materials at the end.
    - Addison Wesley Longman, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Against the Wall, undated (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - Alexander Verlag Berlin, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - Ambassade de France, 1962-2005 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - American Airlines, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - The American University, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Andere Sinema, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - Anthology Film Archives, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - L'Arc, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - L'Arche, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - Armand Collier, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - Artists Talk on Art, Inc., 1985 (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - Artspace, 1991-5 (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - Athenaeum, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 136)
    - The Banff Centre, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - Beaux Arts, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - Better Business Bureau of Chicago, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - Better Business Bureau of Metropolitan New York, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - [Bokcafet Svarta Manen], 1983 (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - Brandeis University, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - Brown University, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - Bucherbogen am Savignyplatz GmbH, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - Le Bureau du Livre Français, 1985-97 (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - Cal Arts, 1983; 1991 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Calhoun School, 1984-5 (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Camera Obscura, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - Carnegie-Mellon University, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - Case Western Reserve University, 1969-72 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - Cassandre, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - Castillo Theatre, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - Center for Arts Information, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - Center for Contemporary Arts of Santa Fe, 1993-4 (Box 6, Folder 154)
    - Centre Georges Pompidou, 1987-9 (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - Centre International de Semiotique et de Linguistique, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - Centre Michel Foucault, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - Char Wulf Mechanical, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 158)
    - Christian Bourgeois Editeur, 1987-9 (Box 6, Folder 159)
    - Church Management Corp., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 161)
    - City Lights Booksellers, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 162)
    - Colgate University, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 163)
    - Columbia University, 1968-78 (Box 6, Folder 164)
    - Columbia University, 1980-9 (Box 6, Folder 165)
    - Columbia University, 1991-2001 (Box 6, Folder 166)
    - Columbia University Press, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 167)
    - Con Edison, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 168)
    - Conference of Socialist Economists, Books, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 169)
    - The Conscious Collective, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 170)
    - Le Consulat Culturel (annotations on verso), 1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - The Cooper Union, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Coordinating Council of Literary Magazines (CCLM), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Cornell University, 1977-83 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Cosmopolis Conference, 1999; ` (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Critical Texts, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - CUNY, 1970-2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Dartmouth College, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Delectus Books, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Der Lowe, [1983] (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Deutscher Akademischer Austaushdienst (DAAD), 1985 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Diacritics, 1973-93 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Documents, 1991-3 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Drexel University, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Duke University, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Ecole Chantelemerle, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Editions Almann-Levy, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Editions Autrement, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Editions Bernard Grasset, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Editions de Minuit, 1971-86 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Editions Dominique Bedou, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Editions du Seuil, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Editions Galilee, 1981-9 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Editions Gallimard, 1963-98 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Editions la Decouverte, 1990-8 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Editions Payot, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Editions Plon, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Editions Pluriel, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Editora Brasiliense, 1987-9 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Effects, Magazine for New Art Theory, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - The English Agency (Japan) Ltd., 1991-2 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Especes Nomades, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - European American Student Club, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - European Media Art Festival, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Evolutionary Blues, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Fairleigh Dickinson University, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Feral Publications, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Festival International du Nouveau Cinema de Montreal, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Field Day Review, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Fitac Guadalajara, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - FGSU, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Flash Art, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Found Object, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Foundation for Art Resources, Inc., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - France Edition, Inc., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Free Association Books, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Free Media Forum, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - French-American Foundation, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - French Cultural Service, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - French Institute / Alliance Française, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - George Mason University, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Georges Borchardt Inc., 1975-88 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Gondolat-Jel, 1994-5 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Goucher College, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Grand Street, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Grazer Kunstverein, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Griffith University, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Grove Atlantic Inc., 2002 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Guggenheim Foundation, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Harvard University, 1968-98 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Haverford College, 1968-9 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Himal, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Home News Planet, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Humanities in Society, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - ICA Gallery, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Illuminations/ State of the Art, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - In This Corner, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Institute of Contemporary Art, Boston, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Institute for Creative Misunderstanding, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Institute for Scientific Information, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - International Center for 8mm Film and Video, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - International Masoch Fund, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Ithaca College, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Jan van Eyck Akademie, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Jeu de Paume, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - John Amslow & Assoc. (mail order sex toys), undated (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Le Journal Français, undated (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Journal of Contemporary Studies, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - The Kitchen, undated (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Kodak, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Kunsthalle Wein, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Kunstverein München, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - L.A. Catalyst, undated (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - La Fabrique, Editions, undated (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Lapis Press, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Last Issue, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - LBudd et. al., 1979-96 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Left Hand Books, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - L.E.S. Radio, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - The Living Theatre, 1988-90 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Longman Group UK Ltd., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Los Angeles Reader, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Loughborough University, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Lusitania Press Inc., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - McGraw-Hill, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Mercure de France, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Merve-Verlag, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Metropolitan Life Insurance, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Midwest, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Ministere des Affaires Etrangeres (France), 1975 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - M.I.T. Press, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Modern Languages Association (MLA), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - Mohrbooks, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - MPB Film Books, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Museum of Contemporary Art at California Plaza, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - The Nation, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - New Line Cinema, undated (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - New Mexico State University, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - New Museum, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - New York Public Library, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Newberry Library, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Northwestern University, 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Le Nouvel Observateur, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Now Time, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - nyhabitat.com, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Ohio State University, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Oktagon, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Open University Press, 1992-3 (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - Parachute, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Paragon House, 1987-91 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Parallax, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Pearson Custom Publishing, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Pennsylvania State University, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - The Poetry Project, c. 1988 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Polity Press, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Pomona College, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Princeton University, 1968-9 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - Princeton University Press, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Review of Existential Psychology and Psychiatry, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - Rice University, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation, 1987-8 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Routledge & Kegan Paul Ltd., 1982 (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - Rowohlt, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - Rutgers University, 1970-86 (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - Sans Serif Inc., undated (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - Sapio, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - School of Visual Arts, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 141)
    - Schuh Real Estate, undated (Box 7, Folder 142)
    - Semiotic Society of America, 1977-82 (Box 7, Folder 143)
    - Semiotica, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 144)
    - Smith College, 1968-70 (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - La Societe de Conservation du Present, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 146)
    - Societe Nouvelle des Editions Pauvert, 1992-6 (Box 7, Folder 147)
    - Sony Corporation, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 148)